Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 1950-2004; 2; 3.5 cubic ft.
  - Notes on Ualbany Basketball Coaches, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 52)
  - NY Giants Summer Training Camp, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 53)
  - N.Y.S Association of Intercollegiate Athletics for Women NYSAIAW ( I), 1971-1973 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 54)
  - Press Passes, 1969-1971 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 55)
  - Public Relations, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 56)
  - NYSAIAW (II), 1971-1973 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 57)
  - Public Relations, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 58)
  - Public Relations, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 59)
  - Recreation Program: Summer Activities, 1966; 1973 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 60)
  - Recruitment, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 61)
  - Recruitment, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 62)
  - Robert Ford Correspondence, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 63)
  - Roster and Athlete Stats, ca. 1999 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 64)
  - Roster and Athlete Stats, ca. 2000s (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 65)
  - Sabbatical, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 66)
  - Sailing Club, 1967-1970 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 67)
  - Schedules, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 68)
  - Schedules, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 69)
  - Schedule, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 70)
  - Sports Bulletin-SportsCast, 1968 May (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 71)
  - Sports General Information, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 72)
  - Sports Information + Rules, 1912-1923 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 73)
  - State Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 74)
  - Student Association Finacial Statements, 1972 June 30 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 75)
  - Student Association, 1971 -1973 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 76)
  - Summer Planning Conference, 1969-1973 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 77)
  - Summer Planning Conference Department of Physical Education, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 78)
  - Summer Session, 1965-1967 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 79)
  - SUNYAC Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 80)
  - SUNYAC EXEC. Committee, 1970-1974 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 81)
  - SUNYAC Finances, 1970-1974 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 82)
  - SUNYAC Tournaments, 1970-1974 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 83)
  - SUNYAC Awards, 1972 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 84)
  - SUNYAC Constitution, 1972 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 85)
  - SUNYAC EXEC. Committee, 1972 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 86)
  - SUNYAC Annual Meeting State University of New York at Albany Athletics Conference, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 87)
  - SUNYAC Publicist-Coach Accolades, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 88)
  - Visiting Groups: Summer Session, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 89)
  - Swimming Coach Evaluation, 1971-1972 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Team Captains, 1971-1972 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - Team Records and All Time Scoring Leaders, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - Team Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - Team Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Team Rosters, 1952-1968 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Team Rosters, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - Team Rosters, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - Team Rosters, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Team Rosters, 1971-1972 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Team Rosters, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Transportation, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Transportation, 1971-1972 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Varsity Athletics Contracts: Analysis, 1950-1967 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - Varsity Athletics Clippings, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Varsity Soccer: Albany - Montclair Game Report on, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Varsity Soccer "All- America" Nominees, 1966 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Varsity Soccer: Approved Soccer Officials, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Varsity Soccer Clinics: A Study Guide for (Joseph Garcia's Master Thesis), Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Varsity Soccer: Clippings + Photos, 1964 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Varsity Soccer Conferences: NSCA "All America", 1950-1958 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Varsity Soccer Conferences: NYSIAC, 1959-1960 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - Varsity Soccer Conferences: SUNYAC "All-Star", 1963 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Varsity Soccer Conferences: National Soccer Coaches Association of America " All N.Y.S." ( NSCAA), 1963-1964 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Varsity Soccer Conference: ECAC Awards Committee, 1964 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Varsity Soccer: Dance + Coordination, 1964 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Varsity Soccer: Soccer Manual, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Varsity Soccer: Pre-Season Mailing, 1966-1967 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Varsity Soccer Scheduled Absences, 1966 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - Varsity Sports Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Varsity Wrestling Championships + Tournaments, 1962 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - Varsity Wrestling: Clippings, 1966 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - Wrestling Photographs, 1961-1962 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - Wrestling Publicity, 1971-1974 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Varsity Wrestling Post-Season Tournaments Request, 1966 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Varsity Wrestling Pre-Season Practice: Letters, 1965 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - Varsity Wrestling SUNYA Wrestling Clinics, 1969 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - Varsity Wrestling: Survey + Technique, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Warren W. Crow (Wrestling) (Resumee), Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Women's Sports Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Annual Report (Women's Intercollegiate Athletics), 1967-1968 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Annual Report (WAA) includes WAA Constitution (4/26/68), 1967-1968 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Women's Intercollegiate Report, 1967-1968 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Women's Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - NYS Association of Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, 1976-1977 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Women's Varsity Sports Organization of New York State Colleges (WVSONYSC) (I), 1969-1971 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Sports Crew Men/Women, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - WVSONYSC (II), 1964-1972 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Won-Lost by Season, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - NY Senate Proclamation for Bobford Retirement, ca. 1999-2000 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - State of New York Legislature, 1978 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
- Athletic Advisory Board, 1952-1977; 3; 0.75 cubic ft.
  Arranged Chronologically.
  Contains predominantly minutes of the Athletic Advisory Board (A.A. Board) from 1955 to 1976, maintained by the Director of Athletics in his function as Secretary of the Board, as well as supporting budgets, correspondence, memoranda, and scattered A.A. Board reports, 1952, 1955-1976.
  Correspondents include Dr. Alfred Werner, Director of Athletics, and Joseph Garcia, Coordinator of Varsity Athletics, as well as the coaching staff. Also contained in the records are of the Athletics, and the Final Report of the University Athletics Council in regarding to the inter-collegiate sports (May 1968).
  Also included are lists of sports rosters, and the outstanding athletics who received awards at the Annual AA Board "All Sports Banquet."
  - Criteria for Intercollegiate Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 1)
  - Athletic Awards-Correspondence, 1969; 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 2)
  - A.A. Bd. All Sports Banquet includes sport results, outstanding teams, most improved players, 1970 May 20 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 3)
  - A.A. Board Minutes and Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 4)
  - AA Board Minutes, Proposals and Memoranda, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Information includes correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 6)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Memoranda and Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 7)
  - A.A. Board Finance Policy, 1973 March (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 8)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Proposals and Memoranda, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 9)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Memoranda and Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 10)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Memoranda and Miscellaneous includes proposal for volleyball for men and woman becomes athletic Finance Committee, Nov. 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 11)
  - AFC Proposals, Memoranda, Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 12)
  - A.A. BD: Objectives of the Intercollegiate Athletic Program, Undated (Box 1 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 13)
  - Semi-Annual Report of The State College AAB, 1952 October (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 1)
  - AAB Compiled Minutes, 1955-1969 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 2)
  - A.A. Board Minutes includes (12/3/64) document about incorporation of football as a variety sport at university, 1964-1965 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 3)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 4)
  - Rf. Control of Intercollegiate Athletics Report to Vice President of Student Affairs, 1966 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 5)
  - A.A. Banquet, 1966 May 24; 1967 March 21 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 6)
  - A.A. Board Minutes and Memoranda, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 7)
  - A.A. Board- All Sports Banquet, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 8)
  - A.A. Board Minutes Memos and Proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 9)
  - Final Report of the University Athletics Council, 1968 May (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 10)
  - All Sports Banquet, 1968 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 11)
  - A.A. Board Minutes, Proposals and Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 12)
  - A.A. Board Report to Central Council RE: Budget- General Statements, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 13)
  - Constitution Women's Varsity Sports Organization of N.Y.S, 1969 January 15 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 14)
  - All Sports Banquet, 1969 May 22 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 15)
  - A.A. Board Minutes and Memorands, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (3-Athletic Advisory Board), Folder 16)
- Mens' Sports, 1954-1986; 4; 3 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by sport.
  The files were retained by the Director of Athletics Alfred Werner, and Coordinator/Associate Director/Director Joe Garcia. They contain correspondence, memorandum, Sportscast, sports information publicity forms, sports schedules, and sports statistic books.
  - 1986 ECAC Division III Upstate Men's Basketball All-Star Team (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 1)
  - 1985 Men's All- SUNYAC Basketball Team, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 2)
  - 1986 New York State Division III All State Basketball Team (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 3)
  - Baseball, 1966-1977 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 4)
  - Baseball, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 5)
  - Fall Baseball, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 6)
  - Baseball, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 7)
  - Fall Baseball, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 9)
  - Baseball, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 10)
  - SUNYAC Baseball, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 11)
  - Fall Baseball, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 12)
  - Fall Baseball, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 13)
  - Baseball, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 14)
  - Fall Baseball, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 15)
  - Baseball, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 16)
  - Baseball, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 17)
  - Baseball, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 18)
  - Baseball, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 19)
  - Fall Baseball, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 20)
  - Baseball, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 21)
  - Baseball, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 22)
  - Fall Baseball, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 23)
  - Baseball, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 24)
  - Basketball, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 25)
  - Basketball Rosters and Awards, 1967-1977 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 26)
  - Basketball, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 27)
  - Basketball, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 28)
  - SUNYAC Basketball, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 29)
  - Basketball, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 30)
  - Basketball Pass Letters to Coaches, 1970-1974 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 31)
  - Basketball, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 32)
  - Basketball, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 33)
  - Basketball Albany vs. Oneonta, 1976 November 24 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 34)
  - Basketball Albany vs. Geneseo, 1976 December 11 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 35)
  - Basketball vs. S. Conn 11/29/78, vs. Cortland 12/2/78, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 36)
  - Basketball vs. Binghamton 12/6/78, Geneseo 12/9/78, Hartwick 12/13/78, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 37)
  - Basketball Cap. Dist. Journey 1/5-6/79 Florida 1/8-13/79, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 38)
  - Basketball vs. Oneonta 1/23/79, Brockport 1/25/79, Post 1/27/79, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 39)
  - Basketball vs. Postdam 2/16/79, Plattsburgh 2/20/79, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 40)
  - Basketball vs. Hamilton 1/16/79, Buffalo 1/18/79, Colgate 1/20/79, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 41)
  - Basketball vs. Union 1/31/79, Fredonia 2/3/79, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 42)
  - Basketball vs. RPI 2/6, Elmira Tourney 2/10-11/79, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 43)
  - Basketball vs. Binghamton 2/22/79, Oswego 2/24/79, Utica 2/27/79, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 44)
  - Basketball NCAA DIV. III Tourn. Danville, KY, 1979 March 2-3 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 45)
  - Basketball Statistics, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 46)
  - Basketball- Men's Varsity Roster [Restricted], 1986-1987 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 47)
  - Basketball-New York State Division III All Freshman Team, Undated (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 48)
  - Basketball-Player Records, Undated (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 49)
  - Basketball Roster by Year, Undated (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 50)
  - Basketball-Score Leaders, Undated (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 51)
  - Cross-Country, 1962-1975 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 52)
  - Cross-Country, 1967-1986 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 53)
  - Cross-Country, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 54)
  - Cross-Country, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 55)
  - Cross-Country, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 56)
  - SUNYAC Cross Country, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 57)
  - Cross-Country Invitational Run Includes History of Sport at Albany 1962-1971, 1971 October 30 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 58)
  - Cross-Country, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 59)
  - Cross-Country, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 60)
  - Cross-Country, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 61)
  - Cross-Country, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 62)
  - Final Varsity Basketball Statistics, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 63)
  - Football Statistics Book, 1970 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 64)
  - Football (1st YR), 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 65)
  - Football: Utica, 1971 September 25 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 66)
  - Football: RIT, 1971 October 2 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 67)
  - Football: Niagra, 1971 October 9 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 68)
  - Football: Adelphi, 1971 October 16 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 69)
  - Football: Siena, 1971 October 30 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 70)
  - Football: Plattsburgh, 1971 November 6 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 71)
  - Football: HVCC, 1971 November 13 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 72)
  - Football: Pace, 1971 November 20 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 73)
  - Football, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 74)
  - Football, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 75)
  - Football: STDNYBrook, 1972 September 23 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 76)
  - Football: RIT, 1972 September 30 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 77)
  - Football: Niagara, 1972 October 7 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 78)
  - Football: HVCC, 1972 October 14 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 79)
  - Football: Brockport, 1972 October 21 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 80)
  - Football: Pace, 1971 October 28 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 81)
  - Football: Siena, 1972 November 4 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 82)
  - Football: Plattsburgh, 1972 November 11 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 83)
  - Football Information, 1972 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 84)
  - Football: Stonybrook Patriots, 1973 September 22 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 85)
  - Football: Nichols Bisons, 1973 September 29 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 86)
  - Football: Niagra Purple Eagles, 1973 October 6 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 87)
  - Football: Siena Indians, 1973 October 13 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 88)
  - Football: Curry Colonels, 1973 October 20 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 89)
  - Football: Brockport Golden Eagles, 1973 October 27 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 90)
  - Football: RIT Tigers, 1973 November 3 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 91)
  - Football: Plattsburgh Cardinals, 1973 November 10 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 92)
  - Football: RPI Engineers, 1973 November 17 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 93)
  - Football: Hostra Flying Dutchmen, 1974 September 21 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 94)
  - Football: Alfred Saxons, 1974 September 28 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 95)
  - Football: RIT Tigers, 1974 October 5 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 96)
  - Football: Mass. Maritime Buccaneers, 1974 October 12 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 97)
  - Football: Nichols Bisons, 1974 October 19 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 98)
  - Football: Brockport Golden Eagles, 1974 October 26 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 99)
  - Football: Curry Colonels, 1974 November 2 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 100)
  - Football: Plattsburgh Cardinals, 1974 November 9 (Box 1 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 101)
  - Football: RPI Engineers, 1974 November 16 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 1)
  - Football: Alfred Saxons, 1975 September 13 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 2)
  - Football: Ithaca Bombers, 1975 September 20 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 3)
  - Football: Brockport Golden Eagles, 1975 September 27 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 4)
  - Football: RIT Tigers, 1975 October 4 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 5)
  - Football: Southern Conn. Owls, 1975 October 18 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 6)
  - Football: Norwich Cadets, 1975 October 25 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 7)
  - Football: Albright Lions, 1975 November 1 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 8)
  - Football: Plattsburgh Cardinals, 1975 November 8 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 9)
  - Football: Springfield Chiefs, 1975 November 15 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 10)
  - Football: Southern Conn., 1976 September 11 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 11)
  - Football: Ithaca, 1976 September 18 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 12)
  - Football: Brockport, 1976 September 25 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 13)
  - Football: RIT, 1976 October 2 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 14)
  - Football: Cortland, 1976 October 16 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 15)
  - Football: Norwich, 1976 October 23 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 16)
  - Football: Plattsburgh, 1976 November 6 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 17)
  - Football: Springfield, 1976 November 13 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 18)
  - Football, 1976 October 30 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 19)
  - Golf, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 20)
  - Golf, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 21)
  - Golf, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 22)
  - Golf, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 23)
  - Golf, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 24)
  - SUNYAC Golf, 1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 25)
  - Golf, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 26)
  - Golf, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 27)
  - Golf, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 28)
  - Golf, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 29)
  - Golf, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 30)
  - Golf, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 31)
  - Lacrosse, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 32)
  - Lacrosse, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 33)
  - Lacrosse, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 34)
  - Lacrosse, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 35)
  - Lacrosse, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 36)
  - Lacrosse, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 37)
  - Lacrosse, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 38)
  - Lacrosse, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 39)
  - Lacrosse, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 40)
  - Lacrosse, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 41)
  - Lacrosse, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 42)
  - Sailing Club, 1967-1969 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 43)
  - Sailing Club, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 44)
  - Sailing Club, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 45)
  - Sailing Club, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 46)
  - Sailing Club, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 47)
  - Soccer, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 48)
  - Soccer, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 49)
  - Soccer, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 50)
  - Soccer, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 51)
  - Soccer, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 52)
  - SUNYAC Soccer, 1970-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 53)
  - Soccer, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 54)
  - Soccer, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 55)